<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Kateringin</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->

    <string name="terms_and_conditions">
    <![CDATA[
    \n
        Terms and Conditions of Use for Kateringin Application\n\n
        Last updated on March 12, 2024\n\nIntroduction\n\n
        Thank you for using the Kateringin application. This application is designed to provide a platform that connects users with various micro, small, and medium enterprises (MSMEs) in the catering industry. Before you continue using this application, we ask you to read carefully and understand the terms and conditions of use listed below.\n\n
        1. Acceptance of Terms and Conditions\n\nBy accessing or using the Kateringin application, you automatically agree to be bound by all the terms and conditions stated in this document. If you do not agree with any part of these terms and conditions, you are not allowed to use the Kateringin application.\n\n
        2. Services Provided\n\nThe Kateringin application aims to provide a platform that connects users with MSMEs in the catering industry. We are not responsible for the quality, availability, or suitability of the products and services provided by third-party MSMEs. We reserve the right to change or discontinue services, either temporarily or permanently, without prior notice.\n\n
        3. Use of the Application\n\nYou are fully responsible for the information you provide to us during the use of the application. You agree to use this application in accordance with applicable laws and will not use this application for unlawful purposes or to harm others. You are not allowed to use this application for commercial purposes without written permission from us.\n\n
        4. Privacy and Security\n\nWe respect your privacy and are committed to protecting your personal data in accordance with our privacy policy. You are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your account information and must not provide access to your account to others.\n\n
        5. Changes to Terms and Conditions\n\nWe reserve the right to change these terms and conditions at any time without prior notice. Any changes to the terms and conditions will be effective immediately upon us posting the updated version on the application.\n\n
        6. Conclusion\n\nThese terms and conditions constitute the entire agreement between you and us regarding the use of the Kateringin application. If any provision of these terms and conditions is declared invalid by a court of competent jurisdiction, that provision shall be deleted without affecting the remaining terms and conditions.\n\nIf you have any questions or complaints about these terms and conditions, please contact us at +62412312331.\n\n
        Thank you for reading and understanding the terms and conditions of use for the Kateringin application. Please contact us if you have any further questions.\n\n\n\n
    ]]>
</string>


</resources>